<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>0xdroopy</title><link>https://bugs.0xdroopy.live/</link><description>Recent content on 0xdroopy</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><language>en-us</language><lastBuildDate>Tue, 08 Mar 2022 00:00:00 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://bugs.0xdroopy.live/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title> Unauthorization of Oauth Token Leads to Pre Account Takeover without Verifying 🍂</title><link>https://bugs.0xdroopy.live/bugs/bugreporthidden/</link><pubDate>Tue, 08 Mar 2022 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://bugs.0xdroopy.live/bugs/bugreporthidden/</guid><description>
Summary # On Fitbit official website I was able to register with any account without verifying the email because of the vulnerability Broken Authentication. This was due to the unauthorization of the Oauth token with respect to the email address which was being transferred to the server.
Functionalities # On fitbit.com there are 2 functionalities to register in the account. One is normal functionality of email address and password whereas other is the functionality of Oauth by which you can register using your google account.</description></item><item><title>How I Tracked You Around The Globe 🌎</title><link>https://bugs.0xdroopy.live/bugs/how-i-tracked-you-around-the-globe/</link><pubDate>Wed, 02 Feb 2022 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://bugs.0xdroopy.live/bugs/how-i-tracked-you-around-the-globe/</guid><description>
Introduction # Welcome back to my writeups again, I strongly offer my gratitude to you for reading and appreciating my writeups. I was not wondering that I would ever upload a new writeup on my this recent report because I only upload less but more meaningful and knowledgable reports which are distinctivly different from many usual people. As you have read my previous writeup, this writeup is also on Google VRP Program.</description></item><item><title>How I Saved Christmas for Google 🎄</title><link>https://bugs.0xdroopy.live/bugs/how-i-saved-the-christmas-for-google/</link><pubDate>Sat, 25 Dec 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://bugs.0xdroopy.live/bugs/how-i-saved-the-christmas-for-google/</guid><description>
Introduction # It was a cold winter morning. I woke up early as I had to start my journey on a great program which was none other than Google Vrp. I read many blog posts on google by different amazing authours and then hunting on google came on my mind. Usually I am not a type of pentester who looks for low hanging bugs, rather I go for them having higher impact and higher difficulty in finding.</description></item></channel></rss>